How far would you go to protect your home?
Homefront is a action, thriller film directed by Gary Fleder.
Phil Broker, a retired DEA agent, leads a quiet life with his daughter Maddy, until a school bullying
incident draws them into a conflict with Morgan “Gator” Bodine, a local crime boss.
Phil Broker, played by Jason Statham.
Morgan 'Gator' Bodine, played by James Franco.
Maddy Broker, played by Izabela Vidovic.
Cassie Bodine Klum, played by Kate Bosworth.
Jimmy Klum, played by Marcus Hester.
Sheriff Keith Rodriguez, played by Clancy Brown.
Homefront is a 2013 American action thriller film directed by Gary Fleder and written by Sylvester
Stallone, who also produced the film with Kevin King Templeton and John Thompson.
The film, which is based on the novel of the same name by Chuck Logan, stars
Jason Statham, James Franco, Winona Ryder, and Kate Bosworth.
In the film, Phil Broker, a retired Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) agent, leads a peaceful life with his daughter Maddy, but
trouble ensues as Broker and Maddy get entangled with Gator Bodine, a crime boss, due to a school bullying incident.
Filming began on October 1, 2012 in New Orleans, Louisiana.
Homefront was released on November 27, 2013.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, daughter, based on
novel or book, police, parent child relationship.
The tone is intense.